A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Asian Cultural Program, 1966-1974; 09; 0.5 Cubic Feet 1 document case
  - Chang Kook Kim - Concert in Geneva (Switzerland) Concourse, circa December 19, 1969; audio recording (Box AT 1, Folder 1)
    RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - Festival Chamber Players - Concert, 1973; audio recording (Box AT 1, Folder 2)
  - 2 Prints by C. K. Bae, 1969 (Box OS 1, Folder 9)
  - Slides - Teo Chin Chye (Artist from Singapore) - Artwork, n.d.; 30 __Slides; photographs (Box S 1, Folder 1)
    File Plan note
    Key to slides in box.
  - Slides - Manuel Ramirez, Jr. (Philippine Artist) - Artwork, 1972; 24 __Slides; photographs (Box S 1, Folder 2)
- Arts in Education Program - Jane Remer Files, 1972-1979; 10; 15.5 Cubic Feet 31 document cases
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged in 3 subseries, as follows:
  Subseries A - New York Project, Subseries B - Public School Projects, Subseries C - Contact File
  The material in this series consists of correspondence, memoranda, proposals, reports, records of meetings, grant files, publications, and articles relating to the Arts in Education Program, primarily in the New York City area or with the League of Cities for the Arts in Education. Material in this series often overlaps with that to be found in Series 11.
  - Jane Remer - Publications, 1973-1978 (Box 66, Folder 537-538)
  - Arts in Education Program - Jane Remer Files - New York Project, 10.A
    - Requests for Participation - Artists, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 539)
    - Requests for Participation - Independent Schools, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 540)
    - Requests for Participation - Miscellany, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 541)
    - Requests for Participation - Museums, 1973-1975 (Box 66, Folder 542)
    - Requests for Participation - Performance Groups, 1973-1975 (Box 66, Folder 543)
    - Requests for Participation - Schools Districts, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 544)
    - Board of Education - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 67, Folder 545)
    - Board of Education - Memoranda, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 546)
    - Board of Education - School Proposals, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 547-548)
    - Board of Education - Letter of Agreement, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 548A)
    - Board of Education - Staff Development, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 549)
    - Board of Education - Correspondence with Irving Anker, 1972-1977 (Box 67, Folder 550)
    - Board of Education - Correspondence with Edythe Gaines, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 551)
    - Board of Education - Correspondence with Edythe Gaines, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 552)
    - Board of Education - Correspondence with Frank W. Macchiarola (Box 68, Folder 553)
    - Board of Education - Correspondence with Arnold Webb, 1975-1979 (Box 68, Folder 554)
    - Board of Education - United Federation of Teachers, 1972-1975 (Box 68, Folder 555)
    - Board of Education - Bureau of Art, 1973-1975 (Box 68, Folder 556)
    - Board of Education - Bureau of Art - School Art League, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 557)
    - Board of Education - Bureau of Curriculum, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 558)
    - Board of Education - JDR 3rd Fund Forum, May 7, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 559-560)
    - School Districts - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 69, Folder 561)
    - School Districts - District #3-M, 1974-1978 (Box 69, Folder 562-563)
    - School Districts - District #4, 1975-1978 (Box 69, Folder 564)
    - School Districts - District #12, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 565)
    - Cooperative Schools - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 69, Folder 566)
    - Demonstration Schools - Minigrant, 1975-1979 (Box 69, Folder 567)
    - Demonstration Schools - PS 41 (Kneitzberg), 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 568)
    - Demonstration Schools - PS 75M (Mercato), 1973-1979 (Box 70, Folder 569)
    - Demonstration Schools - PS 96 (Paley), 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 570)
    - Demonstration Schools - PS 98M (Shapiro), 1975-1979 (Box 70, Folder 571)
    - Demonstration Schools - PS 152 (Shapiro), 1975-1979 (Box 70, Folder 572)
    - Demonstration Schools - PS 312 (Cohen), 1975-1979 (Box 70, Folder 573)
    - Demonstration Schools - IS 44M (Edge), 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 574)
    - Demonstration Schools - IS 152 (Sumner), 1973-1977 (Box 70, Folder 575)
    - Demonstration Schools - JHS 52 (Massana), 1975-1978 (Box 70, Folder 576)
    - Demonstration Schools - JHS 104 (Grill), 1975-1978 (Box 70, Folder 577)
    - Demonstration Schools - JHS 125 (Eidlen), 1975-1977 (Box 71, Folder 578)
    - Demonstration Schools - JHS 167M (Frankenthalen), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 579)
    - Demonstration Schools - JHS 239K (Fischenfeld), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 580)
    - Demonstration Schools - East Harlem Performing Arts School (Kirschbaum), 1975-1977 (Box 71, Folder 581)
    - Demonstration Schools - John F. Kennedy High School, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 582)
    - Demonstration Schools - LaGuardia High School of Music and Art (Klein), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 583)
    - PS 9-M - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 584)
    - PS 9-M - Proposal, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 585)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory (CEMREL), Inc. (Stake/Goodlad Meeting), September 24-October 12, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 586)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Oklahoma City Meeting, October 28-November 1, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 587)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Arts in General Education Orientation Meeting, January 23, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 588)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Dorset Meeting, February 11, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 589)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Glen Cove Retreat, April 20-22, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 590)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Dorset Hotel Meeting, April 21, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 591)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Goodlad Meeting, March 18-19, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 592)
    - Meetings and Traveling Seminars - Arts in General Education Spring Conference, June 8-9, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 593)
    - Touchstone Center - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 71, Folder 594)
    - Touchstone Center - Proposal, January 1975 (Box 72, Folder 595)
    - Touchstone Center - Reports, undated (Box 72, Folder 596)
    - Touchstone Center - Miscellany, 1975-1979 (Box 72, Folder 597)
    - Learning Cooperative - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 598)
    - Learning Cooperative - Memoranda, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 599-601)
    - Learning Cooperative - Miscellany, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 602)
    - Learning Cooperative - Publications, 1972-1977 (Box 73, Folder 603)
    - Learning Cooperative - Information Kit on Alternative Schools, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 604)
    - Learning Cooperative - ED/Options, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 605)
    - Learning Cooperative - Beacon Light Schools, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 606)
    - Learning Cooperative - Correspondence with Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory, Inc. (CEMREL), 1973-1977 (Box 73, Folder 607)
    - Learning Cooperative - Memoranda to Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory, Inc. (CEMREL), 1973-1976 (Box 73, Folder 608)
    - Lincoln Center Institute - Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 73, Folder 609)
    - Lincoln Center Institute - Memoranda, 1968-1976 (Box 73, Folder 610)
    - Lincoln Center Institute - Proposal, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 611)
    - Lincoln Center Institute - Ad Hoc Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 612)
    - Lincoln Center Institute - Miscellany, 1972-1979 (Box 74, Folder 613)
    - Papers, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 614-615)
    - Documentation - General File, 1972-1978 (Box 74, Folder 0615A)
    - Documentation - Learning Cooperative - Dissemination Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 616)
  - Arts in Education Program - Jane Remer Files - Public School Projects, 10.B
    - Hartford - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 74, Folder 617)
    - Hartford - Correspondence with Superintendent, 1974-1979 (Box 74, Folder 618)
    - Hartford - Site Visits, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 619)
    - Hartford - Connecticut Commission on the Arts - Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 75, Folder 620)
    - Hartford - Connecticut Commission on the Arts - Meetings, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 621)
    - Hartford - Connecticut Commission on the Arts - Speeches, 1974-1975 (Box 75, Folder 622)
    - Hartford - Connecticut Commission on the Arts - Miscellany, 1975-1979 (Box 75, Folder 623)
    - Little Rock - Letter of Agreement, 1975-1977 (Box 75, Folder 624)
    - Little Rock - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 75, Folder 625)
    - Little Rock - Memoranda and Notes, 1975-1979 (Box 76, Folder 626)
    - Little Rock - Site Visits, 1975-1977 (Box 76, Folder 627)
    - Little Rock - Background Material, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 628)
    - Little Rock - Case Study Position Paper, 1975-1977 (Box 76, Folder 629)
    - Little Rock - Educational Advisory Committee - Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 76, Folder 630)
    - Little Rock - Educational Advisory Committee - Material, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 631)
    - Little Rock - Curriculum Materials, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 632)
    - Little Rock - Application of Federal Assistance, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 633)
    - Little Rock - Arts in Education Application, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 634-635)
    - Little Rock - Lakewood Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 77, Folder 636)
    - Little Rock - Little Rock Arts Center, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 637)
    - Little Rock - Miscellany, 1976-1979 (Box 77, Folder 638)
    - Minneapolis - Letter of Agreement, 1974-1979 (Box 77, Folder 639)
    - Minneapolis - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 77, Folder 640)
    - Minneapolis - Memoranda and Notes, 1975-1978 (Box 77, Folder 641)
    - Minneapolis - Departmental Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 77, Folder 642)
    - Minneapolis - Minnesota Department of Education, 1974-1976 (Box 78, Folder 643)
    - Minneapolis - Site Visits, 1974-1978 (Box 78, Folder 644-645)
    - Minneapolis - Application for Grants, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 646)
    - Minneapolis - Position Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 78, Folder 647)
    - Minneapolis - Arts in General Education Proposals, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 648)
    - Minneapolis - Report - Artists-in-Residence Dance Program of the Harrison Open School, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 649)
    - Minneapolis - Miscellany, 1975-1978 (Box 78, Folder 650)
    - Minneapolis - Urban Arts Program, 1974-1978 (Box 78, Folder 651)
    - Seattle - Agreement, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 652)
    - Seattle - Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 79, Folder 653)
    - Seattle - Memoranda, 1975-1979 (Box 79, Folder 654)
    - Seattle - Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 79, Folder 655-657)
    - Seattle - Miscellaneous Reports, 1974-1979 (Box 79, Folder 658)
    - Seattle - Position Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 79, Folder 659)
    - Seattle - Newsletters, 1975-1978 (Box 80, Folder 660)
    - Seattle - Curriculum Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 80, Folder 661)
    - Seattle - Site Visits, 1973-1978 (Box 80, Folder 662-663)
    - Seattle - Application for Federal Assistance, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 664)
    - Seattle - Seattle Arts Commission, 1973-1977 (Box 80, Folder 665)
    - Winston-Salem - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 81, Folder 666)
    - Winston-Salem - Memoranda, 1975-1978 (Box 81, Folder 667)
    - Winston-Salem - Position Paper, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 668)
    - Winston-Salem - Site Visits, 1975-1977 (Box 81, Folder 669)
    - Winston-Salem - Miscellany, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 670)
    - League of Cities - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 81, Folder 671)
    - League of Cities - Brochure - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 672)
    - League of Cities - Meetings - Budget Data, 1976-1979 (Box 81, Folder 673)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Comprehensive Arts Planning Project, Washington, DC, 1974 October (Box 82, Folder 674-675)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, March 31-April 2, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 676)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Notebook Planning Session, New York, April 19-20, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 677)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, 1976 May 25-27 (Box 82, Folder 678-679)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, October 18, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 680)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, 1976 December 9-10 (Box 83, Folder 681-683)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Seattle, March 9-11, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 684)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Arts in Education Conference, Chicago, May 3-5, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 685)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Minneapolis, October 26-28, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 686)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, January 11-12, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 687)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Winston-Salem, May 9-12, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 688)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, 1978 October-1979 March (Box 84, Folder 689-692)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Little Rock, April 24-26, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 693)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - New York City, May 17-18, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 694)
    - League of Cities - Meeting - Chicago, May 22-23, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 695)
    - Non-League of Cities - General, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 696)
    - Non-League of Cities - Radio Show, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 697)
    - Non-League of Cities - Boston, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 698)
    - Non-League of Cities - Houston, 1978-1979 (Box 85, Folder 699)
    - Non-League of Cities - Indianapolis, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 700)
    - Non-League of Cities - Lexington, Kentucky, 1978-1979 (Box 85, Folder 701)
    - Non-League of Cities - Oakland, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 702)
    - Non-League of Cities - Palo Alto, 1977-1979 (Box 85, Folder 703)
    - Non-League of Cities - Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 704)
    - Non-League of Cities - Pittsburgh, 1977-1979 (Box 85, Folder 705)
    - Non-League of Cities - Pittsburgh - Arts in Education Conference, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 706)
    - Non-League of Cities - St. Louis Park, Minnesota, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 707)
    - Non-League of Cities - Syracuse (New York) Arts in General Education Program, 1978-1979 (Box 85, Folder 708)
  - Arts in Education Program - Jane Remer Files - Contact File, 10.C
    - Bibliography - Arts in Education, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 709)
    - Fineberg, Carol, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 710)
    - Francis, Abby, 1975-1977 (Box 86, Folder 711)
    - Goldman, Leslie, 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 712)
    - Goodlad, John I. - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 86, Folder 713)
    - Goodlad, John I. - Meetings, 1974-1978 (Box 86, Folder 714)
    - Goodlad, John I. - Institute for the Development of Educational Activities (IDEA), 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 715)
    - Goodlad, John I. - Articles, 1973-1974 (Box 86, Folder 716-717)
    - Goodlad, John I. - Articles, 1975-1978 (Box 87, Folder 718)
    - Greene, Maxine, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 719)
    - Gross, Ronald, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 720)
    - Miscellaneous (H-M) (Box 87, Folder 721)
    - Morrison, Jack, 1974-1976 (Box 87, Folder 722)
    - Oklahoma City, 1973-1976 (Box 87, Folder 723)
    - Resumes (Box 87, Folder 724)
    - Ross, Jerold - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 87, Folder 725)
    - Miscellaneous (S-T) (Box 88, Folder 726)
    - Stake, Robert E., 1973-1976 (Box 88, Folder 727)
    - United States - Alliance for Arts Education - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 88, Folder 728)
    - United States - Alliance for Arts Education - Miscellany, 1973-1976 (Box 88, Folder 729)
    - United States - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 730)
    - United States - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 88, Folder 731)
    - United States - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Artists in Schools Program, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 732)
    - United States - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Task Force on Education, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 733)
    - United States - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Bulletins, 1973-1976 (Box 88, Folder 734)
    - United States - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 735)
    - United States - National Institute of Education, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 736)
    - United States Office of Education, 1970-1979 (Box 89, Folder 737)
    - United States Office of Education - Artists in Education Forum, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 738)
    - United States Office of Education - United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (UNICEF), 1977 (Box 89, Folder 739)
    - Wenner, Gene, 1973-1979 (Box 89, Folder 740)
    - Arts Organization - American Council for the Arts, 1975-1978 (Box 89, Folder 741)
    - Arts Organization - American Council for the Arts - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 89, Folder 742)
    - Arts Organization - American Council for the Arts - Miscellany, 1974-1978 (Box 89, Folder 743)
    - Arts Organization - American Council for the Arts - Conference, 1974-1978 (Box 89, Folder 744-747)
    - Arts Organization - American Crafts Council, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 748)
    - Arts Organization - Arts, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 90, Folder 749)
    - Arts Organization - Arts and Business Council of New York, 1974-1978 (Box 90, Folder 750)
    - Arts Organization - Arts Connection, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 751)
    - Arts Organization - New York State Council on the Arts - Correspondence, 1968-1977 (Box 90, Folder 752)
    - Arts Organization - New York State Council on the Arts - Memoranda, 1968-1975 (Box 90, Folder 753)
    - Arts Organization - New York State Council on the Arts - Meeting, April 3, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 754)
    - Arts Organization - Miscellany (Box 90, Folder 754A)
    - Dance Organizations - Feld Ballet, 1978-1979 (Box 91, Folder 755)
    - Dance Organizations - Miscellaneous Dance Organizations, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 756)
    - Educational Organizations - General Material, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 757)
    - Educational Organizations - American Educational Research Association, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 758)
    - Educational Organizations - Bank Street College of Education, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 759)
    - Educational Organizations - City University of New York, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 760)
    - Educational Organizations - Harlem School of the Arts, 1973-1974 (Box 91, Folder 761)
    - Educational Organizations - Institutional Development Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 762)
    - Educational Organizations - National Association of Elementary School Principals, 1975-1978 (Box 91, Folder 763)
    - Educational Organizations - New York University, 1974-1977 (Box 91, Folder 764)
    - Educational Organizations - Public Education Association, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 765)
    - Educational Organizations - Southern Columbia University Project, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 766)
    - Educational Organizations - Teacher's College (Columbia University), 1973-1978 (Box 91, Folder 767)
    - Educational Organizations - Teacher's and Writers Collaborative, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 768)
    - Educational Organizations - Technical Education Research Center, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 769)
    - Foundations - General Material, 1975-1978 (Box 92, Folder 770)
    - Foundations (A-F) (Box 92, Folder 771)
    - Foundations - New York City Cultural Council, 1973-1978 (Box 92, Folder 772)
    - Foundations - New York Community Trust Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 773-774)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 775)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Miscellany, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 776)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Artist in Schools Program, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 777)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Dance Program Meeting, June 3, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 778)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Emergency School Aid Act (ESAA) Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 93, Folder 779)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 93, Folder 780-782)
    - Foundations (No-Z) (Box 93, Folder 783)
    - Museums - General Material, 1973-1976 (Box 93, Folder 784)
    - Museums Collaborative, 1972-1978 (Box 93, Folder 785)
      Funded by a grant from the New York State Council on the Arts to meet the needs of major New York City cultural institutions.
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Carnival, 1972-1978 (Box 94, Folder 786)
    - Museums - Whitney Museum of Art, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 787)
    - Music Organizations - General Material, 1973-1976 (Box 94, Folder 788)
    - Music Organizations - American Symphony Orchestra, 1974-1976 (Box 94, Folder 789)
    - Music Organizations - Kodaly Institute - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 94, Folder 790)
    - Music Organizations - Kodaly Institute - Proposal to Exxon, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 791)
    - Music Organizations - Kodaly Institute - Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 94, Folder 792)
    - Music Organizations - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 793)
    - Music Organizations - Music America, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 794)
    - Music Organizations - New York Jazz Museum, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 795)
    - Music Organizations - New York Philharmonic, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 796)
    - Music Organizations - Young Audiences - National Committee, 1966-1978 (Box 95, Folder 797)
    - Music Organizations - Young Audiences - New York Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 95, Folder 798)
    - Music Organizations - Young Audiences - Miscellany, 1966-1977 (Box 95, Folder 799)
    - Theatre Organizations - General Material, 1975-1978 (Box 95, Folder 800)
    - Theatre Organizations - American Place Theatre, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 801)
    - Theatre Organizations - City Centers Young People's Theatre, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 802)
    - Theatre Organizations - Cubiculo Theatre, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 803)
    - Theatre Organizations - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 804)
    - Theatre Organizations - O'Neill Memorial Theatre - Center Showboat, 1973-1975 (Box 96, Folder 805)
    - Theatre Organizations - O'Neill Memorial Theatre - Children's Theatre Symposium, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 806)
    - Theatre Organizations - Roundabout Theatre, 1974-1977 (Box 96, Folder 807)
    - Urban Organizations - Henry Street Settlement - Urban Life Center, 1974-1978 (Box 96, Folder 808)
    - Urban Organizations - New York Urban Coalition, 1975-1979 (Box 96, Folder 809)
    - Urban Organizations - New York Urban Coalition - Newsletters, 1974-1978 (Box 96, Folder 810)
- General Records, 1963-1977; 12; 2.5 Cubic Feet 5 document cases
  This series consists of published annual reports and internal records of the JDR 3rd Fund (dockets, minute books, and organization book).
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2252)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 301, Folder 2253)
  - Annual Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 301, Folder 2254)
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 301, Folder 2255)
  - Dockets - Volume I, 1964-1965 (Box 301, Folder 2256)
  - Dockets - Volume II, 1965-1966 (Box 301, Folder 2257)
  - Dockets - Volume III, 1968-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2258)
  - Dockets - Volume IV, 1970-1971 (Box 302, Folder 2259)
  - Dockets - Volume V, 1972-1973 (Box 302, Folder 2260)
  - Dockets - Volume VI, 1973-1974 (Box 303, Folder 2261)
  - Dockets - Volume VII, 1975-1976 (Box 303, Folder 2262)
  - Minutes - Volume I, 1963-1964 (Box 303, Folder 2263)
  - Minutes - Volume II, 1965-1968 (Box 304, Folder 2264)
  - Minutes - Volume III, 1968-1972 (Box 304, Folder 2265)
  - Minutes - Volume IV, 1973-1974 (Box 304, Folder 2266)
  - Organization Book - Volume I, 1964 (Box 305, Folder 2267)
  - Organization Book - Volume II, 1964 (Box 305, Folder 2268)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1961-1985; 13; 0.5 Cubic Feet 1 document case